What? Hayashi, what? You're an athlete candy ball.
They're both low camp.
Too early! Early! Early! Early!
Early!
Why are you crying?
Wait a minute.
I was just looking for a candy bar and a flat tire.
Why are you crying?
Fake Sakuma, come out!
Hey!
He's picking a fight!
Say something funny!
So, what are you doing today?
Yes, sir. We don't have a supplemental layer today, but we'd like to have a little preview of what's to come.
At the end of this VTR, we would like you to choose one grand prize winner for your hard work.
I hope you will pay attention to that as well.
Next VTR, Miki, please give us your V-furi.
The next VTR is the Royal Road Variety Obstacle Race.
The next competition is a steeplechase!
Oh!
Now, this is already quite simple, ladies and gentlemen.
The first course is to find a candy ball on the bank!
The first course is to find a candy ball hidden in the flour by sticking your face in it!
What's first on the causeway?
I don't know!
Doteba, the basic tree
The basic tree, the candy cane search.
Have you guys never done this before?
Arisa has done it before.Arisa is experienced
Leibate.
in such a competition in kindergarten, and she had a field day at a
Unusual kindergarten
I've done "Leibate" candy balls.
You don't like it?
I hate it when my face gets dirty from the first hit.
I like Hibino. She's an idol.
Don't take someone like Hibino who lives for bangs.
The next course is a zigzag worm race.
You take a candy ball in front of you.
You put your body in it and zigzag through the small cones.
And then you circle the big cone at the end.
What? That's hard!
It's not a straight line, it's a zigzag.
The third one is the splash net.
What's that? I've never heard of it.
Really?
Splash net crawl?
When I heard that, I thought it was the splash net crawl.
There's a net over there, and you have to go under it.
And then the splash is attacked from the side with a water cannon.
That is the splash net passage.
And the splash will happen at noon!
Oh, no!
I'm going to destroy everyone's makeup!
Oh no!
And last but not least, a simple bread-eating contest!
Last, last, last, last, last.Last, last, last, last.
Okay, first of all, first round.
You really didn't like yours.
The riffraff.
I'm really doing it.
I really don't like it.
Hayashi vs. Natsume.
The last two will do it for you.
What do you think?
Millimilians win.
Win? I don't know. I've been told.
It's not a contest.
Oh!
Yacchima.
Oh, no!
Don't go. Don't go. Don't go.
It was a two for two thing.
Wait a minute, what was that character?
Natsume and Hayashi are bad too. What's with that character?
Okay, here we go.
In position
All right!
Good luck!
Aah!
Wow!
What's so wild?
Athlete candy?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I mean, not the variety candy ones.
Athlete candy.Athlete Amedamono no Kanata no Kanata!
No!
Hey, I'm not waiting!
Good luck!
This is pretty hard.
Whoa!
Wow!
No, Ryo-kun, a little bit.
Filchu, Filchu.
Filchu?
Don't start!
Here it comes!
Aah! I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
Oh, but you really are as white as an idiot.
You're so cool.
You're so cool. You're so cool.
Wow!
That's great!
Fast, fast, fast, fast, fast, fast, fast!
Oh, you're not making any progress.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
You're such an idiot!
No one flies like Ogisobi...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
And Hayashi's water too
Hayashi...
Don't use your hands!
Don't use your hands, Hayashi!
We'll see Hayashi's diving jump.
Let's go, Natsume!Come on, Natsume.
I can catch up.
Natsume, you can do it!
Natsume!
There's water!
He's gone! He's gone!
The goal!
My mouth is full of powder!
I can't open it!
I can do it. I can do it.
I think I'm gonna cry.
Come on, come on, come on, come on!
Hang in there, hang in there, hang in there!
I can do it! I can do it!
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going!
Goal!
Friendship!
Amazing!
Natsume.
Yes, yes.
Not white at all.
I didn't want to put so much white on my face.
I did.
I hope you're listening to me.
I'm not listening to you.
How can you wear white face?
I can't eat unbun.
Okay, second round...Now for the second match.
The firm and the
Fluffy character showdown
Gentle VS Yoshimura
Go for it!
Come on, Yoshimura.
How confident are you?
I'm scared.
Scared?
My stomach hurts.
Scared of what?
I'm afraid of exposing this candy.
The first candy.
Yoshimura, I think you're exposing it too.
Here I go.
I also see here that the flour is about 5 cm thick.
That thick?
I'll do my best for now.
Okay, let's go then!
On your marks!
Go for it!
Takanashi is getting ready to put his face on, too. He's a setup man, Takanashi.
Setup!
Fast! Fast!
Fast!
Takanashi is fast, too!
And wow! Yoshimura...
Yoshimura, you're so cute.
Takanashi, you're one step short.Takanashi, one step too small!
I see. Takanashi's strategy is to take it in small steps.
Here we go!
This is a good match!
Show us your face! Show us your face!
Show us your face! Show us what you've done!
Show me what you've done! Show me the skin!
Show me what you've seen!
But, what you were saying earlier, since they came to the same place, doesn't that give Takanashi a big advantage?
Advantage, advantage, advantage!
You're right.
You're so cute! Go for it!
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
Takanashi, you're a jumpy one!
Come on!
They're both bad jumpers.
He's so cute.
So cute! Come on! Come on!
That was creepy. That was creepy.
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
But Takanashi decided not to jump.
I can do it!
Yoshimura, go!
Got it! Takanashi!
How's it going?
Was it fast? But it was a pretty crowded field.
Please!
One time with a monamine beam! To the ampersand!
Monamine beam and get low!
No!Oh no!
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
Story! It's great!
It's totally fine, but...
The way Yoshimura's powder is exquisitely applied is the best...
The way the predator in the movie is covered with the powder...
I'm gonna cry.
Yoshimura, what's wrong?
I'm crying!
I'm relieved it's over.
Why are you crying?
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute!
Yoshimura, what's wrong?
Why are you crying?
We were just having a bread-eating contest to find the American.
I had to cry.
I didn't want to get powder on my face.
On your face?
Well... but how did you like it?
She was cute.
Why do I always have to be so adorable?
Pretty is pretty.
I'm sorry I'm embarrassing you again.
I'm sorry. I don't want to get you upset.
Oh, really? You're not mad?
You don't get mad at me?
What are you afraid of?
What are you afraid of?What are you afraid of?
Gross.
No, no, no, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
They'll find us... a little weird.
Maybe that's what people like about you guys.
I, on the other hand, find it kind of funny.
Too harsh! Idols are too demanding!
Being an idol is tough, isn't it?
I didn't know idols were so demanding.
Tell me about it first.
I'm scared!
I'll see you later with Hajime-san.
Sorry.
Take a break.
Sorry we're all resting.
Excuse me and DX.
The second time, I put too much rain in a simple place.
I need a little more of that picture.
And there's one more thing.
The morning bag.
How did the staff do it?
They took it off so fast.
Mr. Takanashi did.
Mr. Takanashi made sure to check there.
We haven't sold that many tickets yet.
Check.
What production company?
Free!Free
I'm gonna crush you.
Free can be crushed?
Free will be destroyed by Sakuma
Free will be taken down by Sakuma.
They'll cut you out.
Don't do this.
There's one person out there who thinks it's real.
It's all over the Internet.
And now, the next matchup is for the honor students.
Nagamatsu vs. Sasaki.
Go for it!
What do you think?
How confident is Nagamatsu?
I'm an honor student, so I'll give it my all.
That's good. You're an honor student.
And Sasaki?
I'd like to see the honor students go head to head.
I'm confident I can win.
I'll do my best.
Do your best to get your face dirty.
If you're Sasaki, you don't have the vocabulary for it.
Let's get going!
On your marks.
All right, let's go!
Snap!
Here we go!
Huh!
I knew it wasn't on!
I'm not trying!I'm not trying too hard!
Nagamatsu wins!
Harajuku Sasaki is doing well too!
That's great!
That's good!
I like the way his face is coming up!
I'm still pushing Nagamatsu.
That's right!
I hope he does well!
I've found it!
I found it!
There it is! There he is!
Sasaki! Got him!
Come on, Sasaki lead!
Sasaki lead!
He's gone! He's gone! He's got it!
Big zag! Big zag!
Come on, come on, come on, come on!
Go! Go!
Go for it!
That's great!
Sue, you're fast!
Looking good!
Sasaki, I'm swinging clear!
Good job!
You're fast! Fast! Fast!
Fast! Fast!
Quick! Sasaki!
Nagamatsu is finally done!
And wow! No!And wow! No!
The long pine tree!
Am I going to get sick here?
Come on! I can catch up!
What is it?
You can catch up, Nagamatsu!
I'm not pulling like that!
No, but here, Sasaki's getting his feet wet here, too!
Come on, Sue!
Almost there! Almost there!
So close!
You can do it!
Sasaki can't jump either.
What, are you going to grab it?
Grab it?
Oh! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
That's great!
Come on! Come on!
Come on!
Meanwhile, the long pine tree is still coming through!
Nagamatsu! Nagamatsu, show us your face!
You're being guessed!
He's sitting down!
You're cutting corners!I've cut a lot of corners!
It's not good!
Last but not least!
Last bread-eating!
I love being covered in long pine powder!
I like it! Covered in flour!
Come on! Come on!
Jump! Jump!
Jump!
Onamifusa iminjus de hikuku!
Till we're stuck!
Until we are plunged!
Thank you, sir.
I can do it! I can do it!
It's not that hot.
I can do it!
It's working!
Goal!
And that's it. That's great.
Very nice.
The powder is good.
The powder is great.
Excellent.
Congratulations to Sasaki!
Next up, former youth high school students face off in Saito vs.
Hizuno, why are you like this?
I'm the leader, so I want to show Mr. Sakuma how good I am
Mr. Sakuma says so. How about you?
Let me see.Let me show you.
I'll show you.
I'm sure you'll say something more interesting.
I'm so scared.
I want to be as funny as Yusa Saito.
I'll do my best.
Go for it.
I'm rooting for you.
Mr. Sakuma, please say something for Hinichino.
I like you a lot, Ms. Hizuno.
Yes, he's funny.
Second round, symbol game.
Gauge, get ready.
Here we go.
Oh?
Oh, shit.
What? Aah! Aah!
No!
Ah, ah, ah, ah
Quick, quick, quick, quick.
It's fast, fast, fast, fast, fast, fast, fast, fast, fast, fast, fast, fast, fast, fast.
Quick, quick, quick.
It's like a mud slurry.
Oh, my God. The only one who's ever done this.
The only one who's done it before.
The best.
Private Avenom.
The Only Experienced
That amount of white
The amount of white on your face is experienced.You're experienced in the amount of white on your face.
Stick to what you show.
Excellent.
Very good.
Penalty. The sun will be the only thing that's interesting.
There's a possibility of tears.
Private Avenom guy is really good at putting it on.
Who puts it on their face?
You're so good at putting it on your face
Privateer Avenom.
Let's go.
It's on Aku.
Oh, Shogo's in my face for show.
He's putting it on his face.
His eyes are all busted up.
He looks scared.
And...
Oh, I knew it.
The best amount of white is great.
Scary.
Eh, Bolt again.
Come on, I'm chasing, I'm chasing, I'm chasing
And then...
Poor thing.
That net up there...
It's like he's trying to rape it.
Yeah, they're not producing enough.
And Saito, too.
Come on, Saito.
He came to the net.It's coming online.
And I'm going for it. I'm going for the face.
Come on, he's going, he's going, he's going, he's going!
Whoa, Saito's getting away!
Come on, Hinichino's still getting hit in the leg here
Come on, whoa. He can't go.
He can't go
Come on, whoa. Maybe he can go.
Could this be it?
This could be a big comeback.
It really is.
Come on. Line up.
Come on, Hinamino! We're almost there!
Saito's in danger!
Can you go?
Can we go?
What'll happen now? What'll happen now?
Come on, this is Hibino.
If we lose, if we lose, if we lose
Come on, man. You can't lose to a human being.
What a surprise!
Saito! The upset victory!
That's great!
Yay!
Saito! Saito! Saito!
Saito! A comeback victory!
Saito, Saito, Saito!
Yay!
Go, go, go!go, go, go!
Hibino
Come on, and give me Hibi's face, and we'll get to the finish line
Let's start the goal!
Saito!
I lost a lot of candy balls.
I couldn't find it at all.
He had a great reaction to the powder, as he had done it before.
He put it on like a croquette that he didn't want to give up.
Mr. Sakumo, how was Hibino?
Hibino... well, yes...
Yes, she did her best.
Gross!
No, not you guys... he's the scariest!
I see...
Eight people are gone.
One more to go.
Well, there's only one left, Fujisaki... but I'm not going to do it alone... so I need an opponent.
Yes, I do. Who do you want?
Who do you want? Come on out, fake artist!
He's considering it.
He's here... he's here... he's here...
Chestnut Falls.
With the recent schedule, there's no way he'll be able to keep his teeth sharp like that.
And he's not even hostile to the production team, he's just outspoken.
I feel sorry for him. He's nervous because he's not supposed to be.
Kuritani, say something funny back.
I'll prove if I'm right. Apologize to me if you lose.
Okay, it's decided. It's not that interesting a fight.Okay, it's decided. It's not that interesting a fight.
Fujisaki's not a bad guy, Kuriya's just a regular guy.
Come on, camera!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Oh, really!
Come on, camera!
Sometimes there's no one there!
With blue skies!
No camera!
Distant iPhone 1
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
What's with the iPhone in the distance!
Ending
I'm losing to Ise-sakuma!
Go for it!
Here we go!
About the position
All right, let's go!
Here we go.
Come on, we can't lose this one.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
That's great.
He's fast!
He's gone! Fujisaki's gone!
You're late, Mr. Sakuma.
Mr. Sakuma, you're missing everything.
All the hair, too.
I can't even tell.
I'll be all over the news.
Oh, no!Oh, no.
It's gonna get around on me.
A woman.
I've got Fujisaki.
Fujisaki's on it.
Fujisaki's ready. Come on, Mr. Sakuma's still a ball of rain.
Goal.
Oh no, yours is as bad as the short face.
That one...
Come on, he's messing around with the water.
I feel sorry for you.
I'm the one who wants to do it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
I put so much white on it, and now I've lost it all with this watered-down version.
So, you know, it's really no good when there's no white left after putting so much white on it.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
It doesn't make sense.
I can't see the front.
Now I can see the front!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Ahh!
Mr. Sakuma, no!
Mr. Bear!
It's over!
This isn't even my imitation anymore.
Aaahhh!
oh, oh, oh, oh!
ahhh!
ahhhhh!
But... but... but... but...Dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee
little............................
A-ha-ha.
What are you doing?
Seriously, what are you doing?
Hey, hey, hey.
I heard they're scared.
I'm gonna cry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Wait a minute, Chomatsu's crying.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
What's wrong? Scared, huh?
You scared me.
I made you cry.
No, you scared me.
Did it scare you when it came out of nowhere?
What did you think was coming?
I don't know, some creature.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Some creature I don't understand.
They thought they were attacked by some creature they didn't understand.
Oh, yeah.
I'm sorry.
That was scary.
And now, the steeplechase!
Thank you very much for your hard work.
The winner of this steeplechase is...
Fujisaki!
In 40 seconds!In 40 seconds!
That's great!
He beat Mr. Sakuma, too.
First place in 40 seconds! How's that?
I can really handle it.
I'm so proud of myself.
We did it. - Yeah, we did it.
I'm sorry... about the crying.
He's really broken up about it.
Yeah, it was a little bit.
I felt bad.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
What? Isn't that a lot of volume?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's simple.
What's the length of the roll now?
You were fast, Fujisaki.
You were fast.
I'm glad you won.
But I'm not sure how Mr. Kritari reacted.
I don't know...
The composition of the fight didn't really work.
The one before the fight started.
Well, you know...
He's not an improviser, he's a preparer.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
I didn't think the riffraff would bring the fight to Agrev.
I didn't think he'd be the one to bring the fight to Agrev.
I was a little nervous.A little nervous.
As a result...
It's not your fault that we got into a fluff fight.
It's not your fault.
You're the one who put up a good fight.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Was that weird?
You were supposed to be human.
You had a really bad look on your face.
It was really bad.
I don't think I could have gotten that good of a shot of him during the race.
It was a comedian.
I had a bad imagination.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
I overdid it.
Hmmm...
But if I give this to the first place winner...
I'd be giving it all to the first place winner.
But this time, it's Fujisaki.
Fujisaki!
Not only did he win that competition.
But also for making Agure fight with Kritari.
He made Agre.
And that last part.
If he were really an idol, he would have been cut.
I'm tired of that pose.
I'm getting tired of it.
It's okay, it's okay.
If you add a lot, the rest won't stand out.The more you add, the less noticeable the rest of us will be.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Just keep adding more.
They'll see the cuts.
Ooh-ooh-ooh!
Too late
First time I've ever been the one who took a wrong turn in this 50 meters
You really are a Papper way to start.
You're a real Papper way to start.
Thank you for watching to the end of the battle to determine the king of sports
I'll be cheering for you guys this time.
Fight! Fight!
Fight. Fight.
Fight!
FIGHT! FIGHT!
Fight! Fight!
Fight Fight Fight
Corte
So, subscribe and rate this channel!
I'm IkeSo!